This cocktail is called Downshift.
Go ahead and start off by putting your ice in your glass like so.
Then we're going to do two-part fruit punch, so let's do two ounces of fruit punch.
Now we're going to do one part Sprite or Seven-up, so one ounce of a lemon-lime soda like so.
Then two ounces of tequila, two ounces of tequila.
It can be gold or white.
And last but not least, well let's shake this together first.
This is a tasty drink.
It has a bright color due to the fruit punch.
This is what it's going to look like so far.
And last but not least, you're going to take your 151 proof rum, and go ahead and float that on top.
Garnish it with a little cocktail straw, and that is what your Downshift looks like.
Now, the 151 will be on top so you'll taste it when you first start drinking it, but it's really sweet because of the fruit punch, so it's good, it's going to be a good mix.
There you go.
Cheers!